realwaystoearnmoneyonline.com 2018-03-23

# Privacy Policy for realwaystoearnmoneyonline.com

**What Personal Information Does the Website Collect and How Is This Personal Information Used?**

The Website may receive and store information that you voluntarily submit through the Website for the purpose of subscribing to the Website to receive newsletters or for the purpose of leaving comments on blog posts.

The Website may receive and store certain types of usage-related information when you interact with the Website, including, but not limited to, your computer's IP address and browser information. The information we collect is used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor.

The Website uses Google Analytics to track statistics regarding our audience and Website traffic. No personally identifiable information is transferred from the Website to Google Analytics. [For more information on Google's Analytics privacy policies, please visit this site](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245).

The Website uses cookies to store visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, customize Website content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends. Cookies may also be used by third-party services, such as Google Analytics, as described above.

From time to time, the Website may engage in sponsored campaigns with various influencer networks, brands, and agencies. All sponsored content is duly disclosed in accordance with the FTC's requirements. From time to time, these sponsored campaigns utilize tracking pixels, which may contain cookies to collect data regarding usage and audience. This information is collected by the sponsoring company to track the results of the campaign. No personally identifiable information collected by the Website is used in conjunction with these tracking pixels.

The Website may engage in affiliate marketing, which is described more fully below. If you click on a link for an affiliate partnership, a cookie will be placed on your browser to track any sales for purposes of commissions.

The Website uses PayPal and SendOwl to service its ecommerce platform. Personal information, such as name, address, phone number, and email address, is collected for purposes of client communication for order fulfillment.

From time to time, the Website may engage in remarketing efforts with third-party companies, such as Google, Facebook, or Instagram, in order to market the Website. These companies use cookies to serve ads based on someone's past visits to the Website. At any time, [you may opt out of Google Ads by modifying your Google Ad settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/authenticated).

**Third-Party Use of Personal Information**

The Website may provide personal information to an applicable third party in order to provide services.

Currently, the Website uses the services of ConvertKit for delivery of email updates. ConvertKit’s use of your personal information is subject to [ConvertKit’s Privacy Policy](https://convertkit.com/privacy/).

As discussed above, the Website uses PayPal for its ecommerce platform. All personal information entered into PayPal will be subject to [PayPal's privacy policy](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full).

As discussed above, the Website uses SendOwl for its ecommerce platform. All personal information entered into SendOwl will be subject to [SendOwl’s privacy policy](https://www.sendowl.com/privacy).

At this time, your personal information is not shared with any other third-party applications. If a new service provider is engaged, these terms will be amended accordingly.

**Will the Website Share the Personal Information It Collects?** **  
** Except when required by law, the Website will not sell, distribute, or reveal users’ email addresses or other personal information without their consent.

RWTE may disclose or transfer personal information collected through the Website to third parties who acquire all or a portion of our business, which may be the result of a merger, consolidation, or purchase of all or a portion of our assets, or in connection with any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding brought by or against us.

**Modification or Deletion of Personal Information** **  
** You can decline to submit personal information at any time. If you decline, RWTE may not be able to continue to provide service to you. You may request deletion of your personal information by sending an email to anna@realwaystoearnmoneyonline.com​, but in some cases, we may be required to keep your information by law. In such a case, it would no longer be active and would be kept separately in an archive.

**CHILDREN'S INFORMATION** **  
** The Website does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that the Website has personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13 in its database the, please contact us immediately anna@realwaystoearnmoneyonline.com​ and RWTE will use its best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.
